Damn, Sun Ming.
That bastard Li Wen dared to set me up.
I'll kill you!
He even dyed it back to blonde hair.
Dandan
Brother Liu
When will you pay the wages you owe me?
I haven't eaten for days.
Brother Liu
You stink so bad!
Let go of me first.
I'll wire it to you later.
Let go!
Brother Liu
Bro.
Bro, bro.
Come here.
Bro, can you do me a favor?
Sure.
Bring me that phone.
Thanks.
What's going on?
I just got the phone.
Bro Liu tied me up here.
I'm trapped here and can't get out.
Bro Liu still hasn't shown up.
Could something have gone wrong?
Hard to say.
Tell you what.
We're coming to rescue you right now.
I'll go.
Let's go.
How did you get in here?
Bro Liu tricked me into coming here.
Same as me.
Bro, can you untie me?
I haven't eaten for days. I'm starving.
Look, I have money in my pocket. Take it.
Just leave enough for me to eat.
Try running now!
Take it easy!
I'll just give you the money!
And you said you hadn't eaten!
How are you this strong?
Bro Dan!
Boss Dan!
I'll give you money!
Take that!
Playing dirty with me!
Bro Dan!
Bro Dan
Where the hell have you been?
Brother Liu
Are you okay, Brother Liu?
Nobody move!
Get down!
Hands on your heads and get down!
What took you so long?
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Where's number ten?
Number ten is Li Wen.
He's at the company.
Officer.
Does this earn me credit?
Bro Liu.
We already have conclusive evidence.
Officer.
I won't resist stubbornly.
I'll talk.
You know the drill.
Start talking.
Our boss is Grass Snake.
I mean, the guy in charge is Grass Snake.
I only took over after he disappeared.
I got promoted, you know.
Our big boss is a psychology expert.
His real name is Yan Li.
Officer.
Can I redeem myself through good deeds?
You have to help me get leniency.
Please make it happen.
Search every corner carefully.
Don't overlook any details.
Understood?
Understood.
Move out!
He's a visiting psychology teacher here.
He comes to the school once a week
to give students psychological counseling.
That's the general situation.
Understood.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You're welcome.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
Captain Sun, Yan Li's addresses are empty.
In that case,
have the traffic department assist us.
Strictly screen all entrances and exits.
Yes, sir.
How does Yan Li always know in advance?
Yan Li has an informant in the city.
I'll send someone to investigate.
We have to root him out.
Get Yan Li's contact info from Bro Liu.
I'll go find Yan Li.
No, doing that is too dangerous.
You'll be easily exposed.
Yan Li hasn't secured his footing yet.
He definitely needs manpower.
If we don't contact him now,
he might cut off all contact at any time.
Can you stop hesitating?
We're very close to the border here.
He could escape at any moment.
I will handle it.
How much longer will it take?
Our funds are being transferred.
We still have many business lines to cut.
It will probably take another
three days.
Remember to destroy the evidence.
Yes, Sir.
Probably one of Grass Snake's men.
Named Li Wen.
Hello?
Hello, Boss.
I'm Li Wen.
The Technical Team Leader of the company.
How...
How did you not get caught?
I'm just a nobody.
Got locked up for a few days and released.
Very good.
I need talent like you.
I'll send someone to pick you up.
Thank you, Boss.
Go to the city
and keep monitoring the police movements.
Then send someone to bring Li Wen here.
Li Wen.
Grass Snake is gone.
Bro Liu was caught.
Yet you still managed to find me.
Interesting.
Boss.
Call me Sir.
Sir.
You're a programmer.
I'm quite skilled.
You'll need me.
Bro Liu and Grass Snake
are both gone.
Yet you're completely fine.
You're quite lucky.
Sir.
Ever since I joined the organization,
I haven't made any money.
I've been to the detention center twice.
I can't even go back to my job now.
I hope you'll take me in, Sir.
Don't worry.
Seeing how loyal you are,
how could I bear to let you leave?
Thank you, Sir.
Do you know her?
I specialize in psychology.
It appears to me you
are more than acquaintances with her.
Sir.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Since you dared to show up,
I cannot be lacking in courtesy.
Now,
I will entertain you properly.
Speak.
Who the hell are you?
Who are you to her?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I just acted on a whim,
using Sun Yao's photo
to test you.
It was your expression
that gave you away.
Sir.
I just wanted to make some money.
Still playing tough.
Beat him up.
If I'm not mistaken,
you must be
the man she wanted to marry.
Is that right?
Sun Yao...
You killed her.